$Apprentice_Agent_Description	Charming when they wish to be seen, and nearly invisible when they do not, agents are skilled in the arts of subterfuge and deception. When threatened, agents strike from afar with arrows coated in deadly poison. As an agent, your poisons last for 50% extra hits.
$Apprentice_Archer_Description	A marksman who strikes from a distance, taking down foes before they even draw a weapon. As an archer, you move 20% faster while drawing your bow.
$Apprentice_Assassin_Description	Swift and deadly, assassins move through shadows to strike at unsuspecting foes. Their short blades are whetted with the blood of previous kills. As an assassin, you deal 25% extra damage with sneak attacks.
$Apprentice_Barbarian_Description	Fearsome warriors who wield Two-handed weapons to inspire fear in the hearts of their enemies. As a barbarian, your power attacks deal 50% extra attack of opportunity damage.
$Apprentice_Battlemage_Description	Protected by heavy armor and armed with Destruction magic, battlemages are a deadly mix of scholar and soldier. As a battlemage, your wards resist 50% of incoming weapon damage.
$Apprentice_Crusader_Description	Heavily armored warriors who use their shields and their keen knowledge of Restoration to rid the world of evil. As a crusader, you resist 50% of incoming arrow and spell damage when you block with a shield.
$Apprentice_Healer_Description	Healers do battle against injury, poison, and disease. The ancient art of Restoration is their ally, and also their weapon. As a healer, your Restoration spells cost 20% less when dual cast.
$Apprentice_Knight_Description	Knights are students of the noble arts of war. In addition to their schooling in letters and speechcraft, knights also learn to care for their arms and armor on the battlefield. As a knight, you resist 10% of all incoming weapon and spell damage.
$Apprentice_Mage_Description	Relying on their extensive knowledge of Alteration magic for protection, mages wield a power more deadly than even the sharpest blade. As a mage, your Magicka Regeneration is increased by 50%.
$Apprentice_Monk_Description	Monks combine the martial and mystic arts, protecting themselves with spells while engaging foes in hand-to-hand combat. As a monk, your Armor Rating is increased by 100 while unarmed.
$Apprentice_Nightblade_Description	Spell and shadow are the nightblade’s friend. Their affinity for Illusion magic gives them a sinister reputation. As a nightblade, your Illusion spells are twice as strong while you are undetected.
$Apprentice_Rogue_Description	Rogues are adventurers and opportunists with a gift for talking themselves out of trouble. When threatened, a rogue’s tongue is as sharp as their blade. As a rogue, you deal 25% extra power attack damage while you have an empty offhand.
$Apprentice_Scout_Description	Cautious warriors who rely on speed and cunning, scouts use bows to fight from range, and shields to protect themselves when the fight comes to them. As a scout, your Stamina Regeneration is increased by 50%.
$Apprentice_Sorcerer_Description	Spellcasters who rely on enchantments and summoned servants for protection. Their desire for power often leads where others refuse to go. As a sorcerer, you have a 10% chance to absorb the Magicka from incoming spells.
$Apprentice_Spellsword_Description	Warriors trained in the art of magic, spellswords wield both blade and spell. Their skill with One-handed weapons makes them deadly at close range. As a spellsword, Destruction spells cost 20% less while you have a weapon equipped.
$Apprentice_Thief_Description	Thieves are pickpockets and pilferers who profit from the loss of others. Unlike common bandits, thieves prefer subterfuge over violence. As a thief, you move 20% faster while sneaking.
$Apprentice_Warrior_Description	Warriors are professional fighters who plow into the fray with little regard for danger. Adept with all weapons, warriors rely on heavy armor to protect them in battle. As a warrior, your Health Regeneration is increased by 50%.
$Apprentice_Witchhunter_Description	Witchhunters are dedicated to rooting out and destroying the evil practices of dark cults and profane sorcery. They do battle with Conjuration magic and potent elixirs. As a witchhunter, your potions last 50% longer.

$Apprentice_Acrobatic_Description	You jump twice as high and take 50% less damage from falling.
$Apprentice_Arcane_Description	Your spells and enchantments cost 20% less, but you cannot regenerate Magicka in combat.
$Apprentice_Athletic_Description	Sprinting costs 50% less Stamina.
$Apprentice_Blessed_Description	Healing scrolls are twice as strong, and you have a small chance to find healing scrolls on fallen enemies.
$Apprentice_Brutal_Description	You deal 10% extra damage with weapons, but you move 10% slower.
$Apprentice_Cannibal_Description	You have a small chance to find human flesh and human hearts when killing humanoids.
$Apprentice_Careful_Description	You take 25% less damage from attacks of opportunity, but you deal 25% less attack of opportunity damage to enemies.
$Apprentice_Charming_Description	Your buying and selling prices are improved by 10%, and you have the power to calm your enemies.
$Apprentice_Craven_Description	You move 10% faster, but take 10% extra weapon and spell damage.
$Apprentice_Cursed_Description	Your reanimation spells cost 50% less, but healing spells cost twice as much.
$Apprentice_Disciplined_Description	You gain 20% extra experience in class skills, but 20% less experience in all other skills.
$Apprentice_Drunkard_Description	Alcohol is twice as strong, but when you are not under the effect of alcohol, your Magicka and Stamina are reduced by 50.
$Apprentice_Elusive_Description	You have the power to vanish into the shadows.
$Apprentice_Faithful_Description	Divine amulets are twice as strong.
$Apprentice_Faithless_Description	You cannot benefit from shrines.
$Apprentice_Favored_Description	You have the power to summon a Guardian Spirit.
$Apprentice_Foolhardy_Description	Your armor is more effective when you are not wearing a helmet.
$Apprentice_Gifted_Description	You do not benefit from your class's starting skills.
$Apprentice_Hearty_Description	Your Disease Resistance is increased by 50%.
$Apprentice_Hoarder_Description	Your Carry Weight is increased by 100, but your selling prices are reduced by 20%.
$Apprentice_Intimidating_Description	You are much more likely to succeed at intimidation checks, and you have the power to send enemies fleeing in fear.
$Apprentice_Milkdrinker_Description	Bonuses from milk are five times stronger, and you find extra milk in your travels.
$Apprentice_Mundane_Description	You resist 20% of incoming spell damage, but your spells and enchantments cost five times as much.
$Apprentice_Prepared_Description	Your Carry Weight is increased by 25, and you find extra cooking ingredients in your travels.
$Apprentice_Reckless_Description	You deal 25% extra damage to staggered targets, but take 25% extra damage while staggered.
$Apprentice_Rugged_Description	Your Injury Resistance is increased by 50%.
$Apprentice_Stormborn_Description	Your Shock Resistance is increased by 50%.
$Apprentice_SweetTooth_Description	You have a small chance to find Skooma on fallen enemies.
$Apprentice_Trollkin_Description	Your Health Regeneration is increased by 100%, but your Fire Resistance is reduced by 50%.
$Apprentice_Venomous_Description	You have a chance to find poisons on slain enemies.
$Apprentice_Versatile_Description	You no longer benefit from your racial passive, but your Health, Magicka, and Stamina are increased by 25.
$Apprentice_Wanted_Description	You receive 20% better prices with fences.

$Acrobatic	Acrobatic
$Arcane	Arcane
$Athletic	Athletic
$Blessed	Blessed
$Brutal	Brutal
$Cannibal	Cannibal
$Careful	Careful
$Charming	Charming
$Craven	Craven
$Cursed	Cursed
$Disciplined	Disciplined
$Drunkard	Drunkard
$Elusive	Elusive
$Faithful	Faithful
$Faithless	Faithless
$Favored	Favored
$Foolhardy	Foolhardy
$Gifted	Gifted
$Hearty	Hearty
$Hoarder	Hoarder
$Intimidating	Intimidating
$Milkdrinker	Milkdrinker
$Mundane	Mundane
$Prepared	Prepared
$Reckless	Reckless
$Rugged	Rugged
$Stormborn	Stormborn
$Sweet Tooth	Sweet Tooth
$Trollkin	Trollkin
$Venomous	Venomous
$Versatile	Versatile
$Wanted	Wanted

$TRAIT	TRAIT
$CLASS	CLASS